Inventory of the Richard Hanser papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Collected material, 1970s (Box-folder 39: 1-2)
- Muth and Haecker materials, undated (Box-folder 39: 3)
- Kuby forum materials, undated (Box-folder 39: 4)
- Notes on indictments, undated (Box-folder 39: 5)
- Chronology radio script, undated (Box-folder 39: 6)
- German notes, undated (Box-folder 39: 7)
- Spiral notebooks, 1977 (Box-folder 39: 8)
- Notes on the Gestapo, 1937 (Box-folder 40: 1)
- Collected notes and research, 1970s (Box-folder 40: 2-4)
- Collected notes, 1970s (Box-folder 41: 1-3)
- German leaflets, 1960s (Box-folder 42: 1)
- "Sophie," quotes, undated (Box-folder 42: 2)
- German notes, 1960s (Box-folder 42: 3)
- Walter Wust papers, 1930s-1940s (Box-folder 42: 4)
- Collected German news clippings, 1981 (Box-folder 42: 5)